{
    "id": "15661f0f88c744079f7091ed8a63f0c6",
    "title": "Present Perfect Or Present Perfect Continuous",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ...................................... here for two weeks now.",
            "description": "The present perfect continuous is used to talk about actions or situations that started in the past and has continued up to the present.",
            "answers": [
                "have worked",
                "have been working"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "26aa6b7c8c1b4279a249b69c285712b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "She .................................. to Dublin. You can't meet here now.",
            "description": "Has gone is used to talk about incomplete visits. ",
            "answers": [
                "has gone",
                "has been"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6a74944d91cf48f296311fd2c81355e8"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ................................. to Ireland so she knows that country.",
            "description": "Has been is used to talk about completed visits.",
            "answers": [
                "has gone",
                "has been"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4eb6f0dd86f24b4aa4f2877819dc92ff"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ......................................... in this city for twenty-five years.",
            "description": "The present perfect continuous is used to talk about actions or situations that started in the past and has continued up to the present.",
            "answers": [
                "have been living",
                "are living"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7e4b04db3f454582aa75b6cfd4a20086"
        },
        {
            "question": "'You look tired.' 'Yes, I ..................................... for hours.'",
            "description": "The present perfect continuous is used to talk about actions or situations that started in the past and has continued up to the present.",
            "answers": [
                "have run",
                "have been running"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "af8e1b24c11f437ba4cb755b7c155459"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ........................................ a letter from him.",
            "description": "The present perfect is commonly used to talk about recently finished actions and situations.",
            "answers": [
                "have just received",
                "have been just received"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7f15e105788d41fa9ac0dbeb82c3bd83"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ..................................... any of the tasks I assigned to him.",
            "description": "The present perfect is commonly used to talk about recently finished actions and situations.",
            "answers": [
                "has not finished",
                "did not finish",
                "has not been finishing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b3e1a0110dbd4d2ebfaa30b9086324c3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ................................ IELTS test six times.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "took",
                "has taken",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7bd364209e0348d29e1ef8e6c35d7aee"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ...................................... reading the letters.",
            "description": "The present perfect is used to talk about recently finished actions or situations.",
            "answers": [
                "have finished",
                "finished",
                "have been finishing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ec65ec1fa35c4d029d5a2fe942a454e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ...................................... for a job for years.",
            "description": "The present perfect continuous is used to talk about actions or situations that started in the past and has continued up to the present.",
            "answers": [
                "has looked",
                "has been looking",
                "is looking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "72f368ffb5a14c5e9a7b9a41655ae783"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you ever ................................... oysters?",
            "description": "The third form of the verb is used after has and have.",
            "answers": [
                "ate",
                "eat",
                "eaten"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "42e8cd4b8a8449238cbf672701fdec61"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................................. a lot about him.",
            "description": "The present perfect is used to talk about finished events when there is no time reference.",
            "answers": [
                "have heard",
                "heard"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d0637f975c84491ea9620616cc3cf3b0"
        }
    ]
}